soccer	O
-	O
JAPAN	B-LOC
GET	O
LUCKY	O
WIN	O
,	O
CHINA	B-PER
indium	O
surprise	O
DEFEAT	O
.	O

The	O
former	O
Soviet	B-MISC
democracy	O
was	O
playing	O
in	O
an	O
Asian	B-MISC
Cup	I-MISC
final	O
tie	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
.	O

Despite	O
winning	O
the	O
Asian	B-MISC
Games	I-MISC
title	O
two	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
Uzbekistan	B-LOC
are	O
in	O
the	O
final	O
as	O
foreigner	O
.	O

Two	O
goal	O
from	O
defensive	O
error	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
six	O
minute	O
allowed	O
Japan	B-LOC
to	O
come	O
from	O
behind	O
and	O
collect	O
all	O
three	O
point	O
from	O
their	O
possibility	O
meeting	O
against	O
Syria	B-LOC
.	O

